In a world of world building, we have to have good questions and good prompts.
And I think one of the things you also have said that I'm caring with me is,
art shows what's possible. But if people haven't seen it, they don't know what's possible.
And that I think is the crux in many ways of this project, which is to say,
there is a world of proliferating images of people making things that try and say,
this is the world I want. And I think this is one of those that does some of that work.
So, and of course, it's echoed through the lenses of one of the people who's doing this work
that we all carry with us. So, maybe you could say a little bit about this one.
I think this is, yeah, a image that I feel proud of. And a lot of my work,
you know, when you say you associate my work with portraiture like that,
is obviously very important to me. And that's how I came into the work, you know,
a lot through asks for memorial portraits from trans folks color, from folks in Black Lives Matter
Movement, from other projects, and and why to be of service. And there's a way that when you
are doing that, you need to be accountable to a certain representational art, like and making
people look a certain way to feel good. It's there's a literalness that is part of that service.
And I have been excited more in the past several years to get to be more imaginative in my work.
And not be so literal. So, I think this piece, I love this piece for that.
There's a there's a Yiddish saying,
as he's dito, a Gansre, Zachwiet, Zabrach in a heart, which is there's nothing as whole as a broken
heart, which this image makes me think of. Yeah, this was a part of that postcard project made for
that postcard project with IC. And Maryum gave us a bunch of quotes, including this one. And we got
to choose. This one took some time just because of drawing all those little crystals.